export const HOOKS_QUESTIONS = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which statement about Hooks is not true?",
    answer_a:
      "Hooks are 100% backwards-compatible and can be used side by side with classes",
    answer_b: "Hooks are still in beta and not available yet",
    answer_c:
      "Hooks are completely opt-in, there's no need to rewrite existing code",
    answer_d: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "b",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which one is not a Hook?",
    answer_a: "useState()",
    answer_b: "useConst()",
    answer_c: "useReducer()",
    answer_d: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "b",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What Hook should be used for data fetching?",
    answer_a: "useDataFetching()",
    answer_b: "useApi()",
    answer_c: "useEffect()",
    answer_d: "useRequest()",
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What are Hooks?",
    answer_a: 'Hooks let you "hook" into a class component to set state.',
    answer_b:
      "New way of doing the same thing. Instead of function methods, we use classes.",
    answer_c:
      "Hooks let you use function components to manage state, instead of class components.",
    answer_d: "Hooks let you make your code more complex and confusing.",
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which is not a React Hooks rule?",
    answer_a: "Only call hooks at the top level.",
    answer_b: "Only call Hooks from React classes.",
    answer_c: "Don't call hooks inside loops, conditions or nested functions.",
    answer_d: "Only hooks from React function components",
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
];
export const GENERAL_QUESTIONS = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which statement about the Agile methodology is true?",
    answer_a:
      "Agile emphasizes incremental delivery, continual planning, and continual learning.",
    answer_b:
      "Agile is best for projects with well-defined requirements where no changes are expected.",
    answer_c:
      "In Agile development all deliverable are delivered after the product is finished.",
    answer_d: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "a",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which one is true about Synchronous vs Asynchronous?",
    answer_a: "Asynchronous means only one execution at a time.",
    answer_b:
      "Synchronous means more than one thing can synchronize and run at the same time.",
    answer_c: "Synchronous basically means only one thing can execute at once.",
    answer_d: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which is true about Web Services(API) SOAP vs REST?",
    answer_a: "Rest was created to address the problems of SOAP.",
    answer_b: "REST is a protocol whereas SOAP is an architectural pattern.",
    answer_c:
      "REST uses service interfaces to expose its functionality to client applications while SOAP uses Uniform Service locators to access the components on the hardware device.",
    answer_d:
      "REST needs more bandwidth for its usage whereas SOAP doesn't need much bandwidth.",
    correct_answer: "a",
  },
];
export const STEPHEN_QUESTIONS = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the name of Stephen's dog?",
    answer_a: "Finn",
    answer_b: "Jake",
    answer_c: "Fluffy",
    answer_d: "He doesn't have a dog",
    correct_answer: "b",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "When is Stephen's birthday?",
    answer_a: "January 1, 1990",
    answer_b: "Febuary 12, 1992",
    answer_c: "April 21, 1992",
    answer_d: "He wasn't born",
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "How many siblings does Stephen have?",
    answer_a: "1",
    answer_b: "2",
    answer_c: "3",
    answer_d: "4",
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
];
